roadhog style
stay out of trouble nana
as long as you get into plenty
[Laughter]
[Music]
nope just thinking of the team
it would help if you did too
you look rich
i gave up my father's empire
and his fortune alongside it
hey big man you got any requests
little silence would be nice
i think i added too much bass to my new
track
no such thing
glitch
you got a problem junker
[Music]
hmm you may certainly try
think i won't
i think you can't
cute
[Music]
cute hook
mako the wreckers want you back thought
you might like to know
they'll hate that i'll pass it along
strike from above you stole a lot of
things that helix was supposed to
protect
you
they've eaten you alive
[Music]
things always go well when you're
working with junkrat and roadhog
i guess it takes all kinds to make a
world
[Music]